SARAH BORGES SILVA



Contact

Rua do Raio, Braga (+351) 910650538 sarahbs@outlook.com

Skills

- Facebook Ads (Meta Ads)
- Google ads
- Tiktok ads
- Pinterest ads
- Google Analytics 4
- Google merchant center
- Looker
- Excel
- Google Docs
- Microsoft Office
- Power BI
- Google tag manager
- Python
- SQL

Education

Universidade do Porto Porto

Master: Data Analytics

Set 2024 - In Progress

Universidade de Brasília

Brasília

Bacharel: Geological

Engineering

Jan 2017 - Jun 2022

Profile

Graduated from the University of Brasília and currently pursuing a Master's in Data Analytics at the University of Porto. Experienced in marketing analytics as a Performance Media Analyst, specializing in data-driven campaign optimization and performance tracking.

Professional Experience

Paid Media Analyst

Savvi | São Carlos, Brasil | Set 2022 - Dez 2024

- Designed, launched, and optimized paid media campaigns across Facebook
 Ads, Google Ads, and other platforms
- Conducted in-depth performance analysis using Looker (Google Data Studio) and Power BI to monitor KPIs such as CTR, CPA, ROAS, and customer acquisition trends
- Interpreted multichannel performance data to recommend optimization strategies, leading to consistent revenue growth

Digital Marketing Manager

White Apex Drones | Luziânia, Brasil | Jan 2022 - Set 2022

- Analyzed ad performance data and customer behavior metrics to identify trends and optimize ad spend efficiency
- Managed client communication

Languages

Portuguese: Native

English: C1

Advanced

Certifications

 Professional Certificate | Google Data Analytics Specialization: Course completed via Coursera.